Guide to the Jennings Wood collection of Confederate imprints, 1862-1865 MS2127
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 828)
  Communication from Attorney GeneralJanuary 9, 1864, [containing an estimate of an additional sum required by the Department of Justice.1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 829)
  Communication from Attorney Genera 1 May 17, 1864. [Submitting estimates of additional appropriations. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 836)
  Report of the Attorney General April 25, 1864. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 837)
  Report on vessels sunk and burnt in the Pamunkey River, by Captain Chas S. Carrington, A. Q. M., under the orders of General Joseph E. Johnston and others. 5 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 848)
  Decisions of Hon. James D. Halyburton, judge of the Confederate States District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia, in the cases of John. B. Lane and John H. Leftwich, in relation to their exemption, as mail contractors, from the performance of military service. Richmond: Ritchie & Dunnavant, Printers. 1864. 14 p. 22 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 861)
  Communication from Secretary of NavyMarch 9th, 1863, [submitting the claim of Mr. Daniel J. Turner for a steam dredge machine, sunk in Dismal Swamp Canal, by order of Commander Thomas T. Hunter, Confederate States Navy.4 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 862)
  Communication from the Secretary of the NavyDec. 21st, 1864, [relative to " a flour and grist mill and bakery," established by the Department, at Albany, Georgia.1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 864)
  Communication of Secretary of the Navy Jan. 31st, 1864 [i.e. 1865.] [covering copies of his correspondence with the Governor of North Carolina relative to "coals of the steamer 'Advance.' 12 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 865)
  Communication from Secretary of Navy Feb. 15, 1865, [conveying copies of the remainder of his correspondence with the Governor of North Carolina, relative to coals belonging to the steamer Advance.3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 896)
  Annual report of the Commissioner of Patents, January 26, 1865. 9 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 897)
  Report of the Commissioner of Patents, January, 1862. 17 p. 21 1/2 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 898)
  Report of the Commissioner of Patents January, 1863. 12 p. 21 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 899)
  Report of the Commissioner of Patents Jan. 1864. 15 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 917)
  Report of the Postmaster-General to the President, April 29, 1861. 44 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1066)
  Abstract of drafts of members of the C. S. House of Representatives, paid by E. C. Elmore, Treasurer C.S., during the recess of Congress, after April 18th, 1863, under authority of act of April 16th, 1862. 2 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1067)
  Additional estimates for the support of the government. 14 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1080)
  Circular about an error having occurred in regulations of March 25, 1863, for carrying into effect "An act to provide for the funding and further issuing of treasury notes"1 p. 21 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1091)
  Communication from Secretary of TreasuryFeb. 25, 1863, [in reference to the amount of funds paid into the Treasury under the operation of the sequestration act.1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1094)
  Communication from Secretary of TreasuryJanuary 11,1864, [submitting condensed estimates of appropriations required for the support of the government for the period from January 1 to June 30, 1864, inclusive.7 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1096)
  Communication from Secretary of Treasury May 10, 1864, [submitting estimate in favor of George P. Evans & Co. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1100)
  Communication from Secretary of the Treasury May 25, 1864, [submitting estimate of appropriation for the purchase of cotton, for the purpose of procuring the means of paying, in coin, the interest on certificates of indebtedness.1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1101)
  Communication of Secretary of Treasury, November 23, 1864, [concerning change of old issue of treasury notes for new. 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1103)
  Communication of Secretary of Treasury November 28, 1864, [covering estimates for additional appropriations required by the Navy Department. 2 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1107)
  Communication of Secretary of Treasury.. .December 28th, 1864, [enclosing estimates of additional appropriations required for the service of the agency of the department west of the Mississippi River, for the six months ending June 30, 1865.4 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1109)
  Communication of Secretary of TreasuryJanuary 5th, 1865, [relative to unpaid requisitions upon the treasury, drawn by the Quartermaster General and the Commissary General. 5 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1110)
  Communication from Secretary of TreasuryJan. 28, 1865. [Concerning an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Navy Department,2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1111)
  Communication from Secretary of TreasuryFeb. 1st, 1865. 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1112)
  Communication from Secretary of TreasuryFebruary 1, 1865, [transmitting an estimate for an additional appropriation required to meet the expenses of the Department of Justice during the six months ending June 30, 1865. 2 p. 26 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1113)
  Communication of Secretary of TreasuryFebruary 8th, 1865, [transmitting estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Navy Department. [Richmond, 1865]. 3 p. 24cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1114)
  Communication of Secretary of TreasuryFebruary 11th, 1865, [covering an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Department of Justice. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1115)
  Communication of Secretary of TreasuryFebruary [sic] 20, 1865. 7 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1116)
  Communication from Secretary of Treasury.. .February 20th, 1865, [submitting papers in relation to certain instructions issued from this department, to carry into execution the tax laws. 8 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1117)
  Communication of Secretary of the TreasuryFebruary 28th, 1865. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1119)
  [Communications from the Secretaries of the Treasury and of War relative to the amount of money forwarded to the Trans-Mississippi Department since the adjournment of Congress, and to the adjustment of claims for articles illegally impressed.14 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1122)
  [Communications from the Secretary of the Treasury and the Attorney General, in regard to the sequestration of real estate belonging to alien enemies.7 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1123)
  [Communications of Secretary of the TreasuryMay 2, 1864, submitting estimates of additional appropriations required for the support of the government.2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1137)
  The following regulations and instructions for carrying into effect the act of February 17, 1864, "to reduce the currency and to authorize a new issue of notes and bonds"8 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1150)
  Letter from Secretary of the Treasury...Jan. 12, 1863, [enclosing an estimate of the amount required for the telegraphic service, to June 30th, 1863.[Richmond, 1863]. 4 p. 24cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1151)
  Letter of the Secretary of the Treasury...December 10, 1863, [covering estimates of sums needed for the public service among the Indian tribes.4 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1152)
  Letter of Secretary of Treasury...December 10, 1864, [showing the additional amount necessary to meet the estimated expenses of the Department of Justice, for the half year ending June 30, 1865.4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1153)
  Letter of Secretary of Treasury.. .December 12, 1864, [transmitting statement showing certain transfers of appropriations required for the service of the Treasury Department.2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1157)
  [Open letter to the banks concerning the act of Congress to reduce the currency.2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1161)
  Regulations as to certificates of indebtedness...May 5th, 1864. 2 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1165)
  [Regulations established in relation to the receipt of four per cent, bonds and certificates offered in payment for taxes. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1168)
  Regulations in relation to the issue of certificates for bonds and registered stock...February 25, 1863. 4 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1172)
  [Regulations prescribed for the government and directions of all officers of the revenue, to carry into effect the provisions of the act to prohibit the importation of luxuries, or of articles not necessary or of common use, approved February 6th, 1864.6 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1187)
  Report on the condition of government cotton, contiguous to the Mississippi and its tributaries...May 16, 1864. 7 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1188)
  Response of the Secretary of the Treasury to the resolution of the Senate of the 5th December 1864, respecting operations under the act to impose regulations upon the foreign commerce of the Confederate StatesDecember 12, 1864. [Richmond, 1864] 7 p. 24 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, undated (Box 3, Folder 1189)
  Revenue depots referred to at page 4[Richmond, n.d.] Broadside. 24 l/2 x 15 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 1197)
  Special report of the Secretary of the Treasury on the subject of the finances January 9th, 1865. 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861 (Box 3, Folder 1203)
  [Tabular statementshowing the rates of duty upon merchandise under the tariff act of 1857, of the United States, as amended by the Provisional Congress of the Confederate States of America; the rates under the proposed tariff bill now pending before the said Provisional Congress; and the rates under the act of Congress of the United States of 1861. Montgomery, 1861]. 47 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861-1864 (Box 3, Folder 1205)
  Treasury circular, no. 1 - 25. [Montgomery, etc., 1861-64]. v.p. 22 cm. DGW: 1, 2, 4, 6, 7, 9, 11, 12 ,14, 19
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1254)
  [Circulars from C. S. Central Laboratory, (Ordn.) Macon, Ga., 1862-63]. DGW: April 30, 1864: [Concerning manufacture of portfires, etc.]
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1264)
  Communication of the Secretary of War January 27, 1863, [enclosing an estimate of funds required by the Ordnance Bureau. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1268)
  Communication from the Secretary of War Feb. 3, 1863, [covering reports from the Surgeon General and the Chief of lEhgineers. 6 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 06/30/1863 (Box 3, Folder 1269)
  Communicationfrom the Secretary of War, February 4th, 1863, submitting estimates for the Indian service to June 30, 1863. 6 p. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1271)
  Communication from the Secretary of War, February 5, 1863, [covering an estimate of the amount required for the remuneration of additional clerks in the War Department. 2 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1274)
  Communication from Secretary of War Feb. 14, 1863, [transmitting the report of General John H. Winder, listing the civilians hi custody, under authority of the War Department, in the city of Richmond. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1275)
  Communication from Secretary of War Feb. 17, 1863, [enclosing a report from the Quartermaster General, with regard to the number of quartermasters on duty in Richmond. Richmond, 1863]. 4 p. 24 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1276)
  Communication from the Secretary of War, [enclosing an estimate of funds required for the contingencies of the Adjutant and Inspector General's Office for the period ending June 30, 1863. Richmond, 1863]. 3 p. 24 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1278)
  Communication from the Secretary of War.. .February 27, 1863, [enclosing a list of the civilian prisoners in custody at Salisbury, North Carolina, under military authority. Richmond, 1863]. 7 p. 22 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1279)
  Communication from the Secretary of War March 3, 1863. [transmitting estimate of additional funds required for the service of the ordnance Bureau, for the period ending 30th June, 1863. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1280)
  Communication from the Secretary of War March 11, 1863 transmitting claims for vessels seized for public use. Richmond, 1863. 4 p. 23 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1284)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 14, 1863, [relative to the exemption of mail contractors under the act of April 14, 1863. Richmond, 1863]. 6 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1285)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 17, 1863, [transmitting a report from Colonel J. S. Perston, chief of the Conscript Bureau, of the number of exempts in the Confederate States. Richmond, 1863]. 4 p. 22 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 3, Folder 1287)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 19, 1863, [covering a list of the officers of artillery in the provisional army, for the performance of ordnance duty, appointed since the 16th day of September, 1862, and the roll of merit reported by the Board of Examiners. Richmond, 1863]. 4 p. 23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1291)
  Communication from the Secretary of War Jan. 15, 1864, [covering copies of regulations and orders relative to the payment of assessments of damages made by commanding officers in the field. Richmond, 1864]. 4 p. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1294)
  Communication of the Secretary of War Jan. 27, 1864, [relative to the "domestic passport system" enforced upon citizens travelling in some parts of the Confederate States outside of the lines of the armies. Richmond, 1864]. 9 p. 23 cm. (2 copies)
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 3, Folder 1295)
  Communication of the Secretary of War January 28, 1864, [covering an estimate of an additional sum needed by the Engineer Bureau. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 24 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/28/1864 (Box 3, Folder 1296)
  [Communication from the Secretary of War, January 28, 1864, stating that the records of his office do not contain any authority to raise troops of conscript age, except in localities where the operation of the conscript law has been suspended. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/04/1864 (Box 3, Folder 1299)
  Communication from Secretary of War Feb. 4, 1864, [transmitting reports from General Sam Jones and Imboden, concerning the prohibition of the transportation of food from the military districts in which they are located. Richmond, 1864]. 6 p. 23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/04/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1300)
  Communication of the Secretary of War Feb. 4, 1864, [relative to the delivery of the "tax in kind" at the government depots by the producers. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/13/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1301)
  Communication of the Secretary of War Feb. 13, 1864, [enclosing an estimate of funds required by the department, for six months, commencing first of February, 1864. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/15/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1303)
  Communication of the Secretary of War Feb. 15, 1864, [conveying information relative to general hospitals in and around Richmond. Richmond, 1864]. 8 p. 23 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 11/14/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1305)
  Communication from the Secretary of War November 14, 1864, [submitting an estimate for the steamer Phoenix. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 11/17/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1306)
  Communication form the Secretary of War November 17, 1864, [relative to the act of June 14, 1864, to provide and organize a General Staff. Richmond, 1864]. 7 p. 23 lh cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 11/21/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1307)
  Communication from Secretary of War Nov. 21, 1864, [relative to the special exchange of prisoners of war by the Commissioner of Exchange. Richmond, 1864]. p.23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 11/28/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1308)
  Communication from Secretary of War Nov. 28, 1864, [relative to the recent impressment of slaves in the State of Virginia. Richmond, 1864]. 4 p. 23 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/03/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1309)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 3, 1864, [conveying information relative to the arrangements which have been made "for the relief of our soldiers who are prisoners of war in the hands of the enemy." Richmond, 1864]. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/03/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1310)
  Communication of Secretary of War Dec. 3, 1864, [relative to the appointments under an act approved June 14, 1864, providing for the establishment and payment of claims for a certain description of property taken or informally impressed for the use of the army. Richmond, 1864]. 4 p. 23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/06/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1311)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 6, 1864, [submitting an estimate of funds needed to meet a deficiency in the appropriation to pay the officers and employees of the department. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/07/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1312)
  Communication from Secretary of War December 7, 1864, [submitting an estimate of funds required to meet our treaty obligations to the Indian nations for the period ending June 30, 1865. Richmond, 1864]. 3 p. 23 V4 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/20/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1314)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 20, 1864, [conveying information relative to the impressment of slaves. Richmond, 1865]. 5 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 12/21/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1315)
  Communication from Secretary of War Dec. 21, 1864, [transmitting an estimate by the Chief of the Engineer Bureau, for the schooner Isabel. Richmond, 1865]. 2 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/05/1865 (Box 4, Folder 1317)
  Communication of Secretary of War January 5, 1865, [conveying information relative to the impressment of brandy. Richmond, 1865]. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/06/1865 (Box 4, Folder 1318)
  Communication of Secretary of War January 6, 1865, [covering an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the Bureau of Engineers. Richmond, 1865]. 2 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/06/1865 (Box 4, Folder 1319)
  Communication of the Secretary of War January 6, 1865, [relative to the passports which have been issued to certain youths to leave the Confederate States. Richmond, 1865]. 4 p. 25cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/07/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1321)
  Communication of Secretary of War Feb. 7, 1864 [i.e. 1865], [covering a list of quartermasters and assistant quartermasters now in the service. Richmond, 1865]. 4 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/14/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1322)
  Communication from Secretary of War Feb. 14, 1865, [conveying information relative to the number of iron furnaces and forges worked by agents of the government or by contractors, during the year 1864. Richmond, 1865]. 15 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/15/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1323)
  Communication from the Secretary of War Feb. 15th, 1865, [transmitting an estimate for an additional appropriation required by the department. Richmond, 1865]. 2 p. 24 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/18/1864 (Box 4, Folder 1324)
  Communication from Secretary of War Feb. 18th, 1865, [conveying information relative to the non-destruction of the cotton in the city of Savannah, before its evacuation by our military forces. Richmond, 1865]. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 1348)
  General orders. Adjutant and Inspector - General's Office. [Richmond, 1862]. v.p. 19 cm. DGW: #1, #95, #100
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 4, Folder 1349)
  General orders. Adjutant and Inspector - General's Office. [Richmond, 1863]. v.p. 20 cm. DGW: #100, #107, #129
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1350)
  General orders. Adjutant and Inspector - General's Office. [Richmond, 1864]. v.p. DGW: #27. #30, #51, #52, #53, #57
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 4, Folder 1351)
  General orders. Adjutant and Inspector - General's Office. [Richmond, 1865]. v. p. DGW: # 5-9
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 06/10/1861 (Box 4, Folder 1358)
  Letter from the Secretary of War March 31, 1862, [communicating copies of the official reports, on file in this department, of the battle of Bethel, on the 10th of June, 1861. Richmond, 1862]. 31 p. 20 l/2 cm. (2 copies)
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1363)